如果我知道 我为政府做的都是下流工作
If I'd known how this was gonna turn out,I'd have gotten some crap job with the feds
再说 我就用枪把
Keep talking like that,I'm gonna put a bullet
你的头打爆
In your head
我知道
We gotta go
有麻烦 是吗?
You're in trouble, aren't you?
维罗妮卡·多诺万?
Veronica Donovan?
你...你是?
Who is this?
我有些可以
I have information
让林肯·布伦斯免除死罪的证据
That will lead to the exoneration of Lincoln Burrows
我必须要检查里面的情况
I gotta check the status in there.
当然可以
It's all good
那么你不会介意我查个清楚吧
Then you won't mind me checking it out.
快把他拉起来!
Get off of him!
把他带走!!!
Get off
快带走...
Get off...
我们今晚离开这
We leave tonight.
迈克尔 我们遇到大问题了
Michael, we got a big problem.
不!
Argh!
退出
Back out.
逃离行动?
Of the escape?
要么就死
Or die
约翰 挺住!
Stay with me, John
我要你挺住!
I need you to stay with me.Breathe
我们一起深呼吸...
Keep breathing
一切都会好的
You're gonna be OK
只要你继续呼吸
Keep breathing
约翰 挺住
Stay with me, John
约翰 加油
You stay with me, John
挺住
You stay with me
Stay with me
为了我 继续呼吸 听到吗?
All right? Can you do that? Keep breathing
You gonna be OK. Stay with me
挺住
Stay with me
就在那里 就在...
Almost there.Almost there.
挺住!
...be OK
他失血过多
He's lost a lot of blood
他这样太危险了
He's hypovolemic
他是什么血型?
What's his blood type?
A型
A neg!
他的血压太低
His blood pressure's too low
他太绝望才这样
He's definitely hypovolemic
我们把他送到芝加哥
We gotta get him to Chicago
要飞大约20分钟
Chicago's a 20-minute flight.
医生 我们得出发了
We gotta go, Doc.
现在只有六个人了
And then there were six.
据我所知...
Far as I know
只有5个
There's five
看你以后敢不敢再靠我那么近!
Don't you ever step up to me like that again.
现在谁是老大 啊?
Who's the tough guy now, huh?
狱长?
Warden?
我兄弟在哪?
Where's my brother?
孩子 他现在有麻烦了
He's in a lot of trouble, son.
你得让我去看他
You have to let me see him.
我无法满足你这个请求
That's not a request.I can grant at the moment.
拜托...
Please
我们要关他36小时 一直到他死刑的那个时候
We're 36hours away from his execution
他现在非常暴躁
He panicked.He got violent
因为这样 他剩下的时间将待在狐狸河
For the rest of his time at Fox River
我们给他严格的看守
We're gonna keep him in ad seg,
为了他的安全 也为别人的安全
For his safety and everybody else's.
但我是他的弟弟
I'm his brother.
我应当可以去看他 那是我的权利
I deserve to see him. It's my right.
直到明天你才有权利看到他
It's not your right to see him...until tomorrow...
在他的死刑上
At his execution
孩子 对不起
I'm sorry, son
他的名字叫约翰·阿布鲁奇 A-B-R-U-Z-Z...
The name is John Abruzzi.A-b-r-u-z-z...
我才不关心什么章程制度
I don't care what protocol is
我就是想知道他现在是好是坏
I just want to know if he's OK
喂? 喂?
Hello? Hello?
医院不愿透露一点他的消息
The hospital won't give out any information.
想知道在那家伙身上发生了什么
Wonder what happened to that boy
就像黑手党的鹰犬
Maybe them Mafia chickens
终归要回到他老家一样
Came home to roost after all
我们要掌握整件事
We gotta put this on hold
哦 放轻松点 我们不是什么都掌握不了
Oh, easy, fish. We're not putting nothing on hold
我认为你没在听我的
I don't think you heard me
直到我把我兄弟从那牢房里弄出来
Until I get my brother out at that home
谁也别想这该死的事
No one's doing a damn thing
我很抱歉 但是他已经回不来了
For god bless sake, but the man is gone
进了那个禁闭室
You go to the tombs
那你就出不来了
You don't get out
直到他们把你绑到电椅上
Not until they strap you up
如果你认为我会丢下我兄弟不管
If you think I'll leave my brother behind
那你就真的太低估我了
You have massively underestimated me
-真的吗?  -真的
-Really?  -Really
耶 但那可不包括在我的行程之内
That ain't my flight
我可以很漂亮的穿过那个牢房 无论有没有你
I'm through that hole, pretty,with or without you
下一次就是在我自由活动的时候
Next time I'm on PI
我们别再这样争论下去了
We're not having this debate
我们不争论?
We're not having this debate?
我们别再这样争论下去了
We're not having this debate
为什么我们不去把那地板砸开
We oughta open the floor
给每一个人?
To everyone else
看看他们都在说什么
See what they all say?
宝贝 你懂吗?
We got a clear shot
我们再不用那个洞
Every day we don't use that hole is another day
迟早会被条子发现的
The screws can find it
这个方法还没结束
The way is not finished
我们都很清楚
We're clear to the infirmary
那个医务室 就是我所需要的
That's all we need
穿过那扇窗户
Through that window
越过那铁丝网 越过那墙
Over that wire, over that wall
你们两个是不可能做到的
The two of you will never make it
哦 宝贝 这不止两个人
Oh, fish, it's not just two.
无论怎么样 我们必须要走
If it's now or never, we gotta go
迈克尔 和我们一起走
Go with us.Michael
你已经做了你该做的
You've done everything you could
大家都是成年人 迈克尔
They're grown men, Michael.
大家都会为自己做打算
They can all decide for themselves
你他妈狗娘养的...
You son of a...
喂 住手 后退
Wait a minute!
你们两个人立刻分开
Hey! Who are you separating there?
嘿 老大 没事没事
Hey, it's good, boss
只是在一起玩玩
Just playing around
没事
It's all good
现在你知道了
You know, there are
这有两件每一个人都必须要遵守的事
Two things that everybody needs to give with here
首先 乡巴佬 彻底地学会尊敬
First, hillbilly,you have got to learn some respect
没有他就没有逃走计划
The man here made everything possible
至于你呢 嫩鸡
And you fish?
现在你必须学会它
You're gonna have to get with that
我们今天下午就开工
We are doing this thing this afternoon
在我们开始自由活动之前
As soon as we get on PI
所以你要冒这个险
So you're just gonna make a run for it
在今天中午
In the middle of the day
伙计 你得这样做
Well, you gotta do
否则你还能做什么呢 宝贝?
What you gotta do, huh, baby?
你会把整个事情都搞砸了
You are gonna screw this whole thing up
你不能再为你自己而替大家做决定
That's not for you to decide any more
现在 我们的事已经进入轨道
Now, this train is leaving the station
我劝你最好和我们一起干
And I suggest you get on it
一起干吧 宝贝 我们一起干
Get on the train, fish.Get on the train.
好啊 你知道什么 你们他妈的狗娘养的
Well, you know what, you sons of bitches?
我不会让你们这么做的
I won't let you do it
你想干吗?
What you gonna do?
边告密
Blow the whistle
边离开这鬼地方
On your own escape?
他会回来的
He'll be back
那些家伙
Those guys
他们今晚会在我们之前从那个洞离开这
They go before us tonight,they use that hole
那就完了
It's over
那些警察会把这翻个底朝天
COs will turn this whole place upside down
直到他们发现那洞
Till they find it
好啦...
Well...
听起来 你一直都在想这件事
Sounds like you're thinking about it
如果我说不 那其实是撒谎
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
我昨天还想从这里逃出去
I want to be out of here yesterday
伙计 我要做爸爸了
I got a kid coming, man
迈克尔 你不可能把他从这里弄出去
Michael, you can't get him out of there.
我可以说吗?
Can I say something?
我知道你并不想听这些
I know you won't want to hear it
但是 呃...
But...
现在他们是非让他上电椅不可了
They're strapping him up either way now
一旦他没了
Once he's gone
你很可能还要在里面再待上5年
You'll be stuck here for another five years.
同样 他们也会根据那个洞查到你
If they trace the hole back to you
他们又将再判你个徒刑
They'll toss another dime.
那可是15年啊 兄弟!
That's 15 years.Papi!
当然 如果我是你
Of course, if I were you
我也不会丢下我兄弟不顾
I wouldn't leave my brother behind either.
不要这要死 不
Not to die like that, no
恩...恩...
Uh-uh
他们对一个男人做的这个世界上最糟的一件事
Worst thing in the world they can do to a man
就是像那样用绳子把他捆在椅子上
Is strap him to a chair like that
我们有事要做了
We're in business
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我刚和我的一个朋友通电话
I just spoke to a friend
他是最高法院的秘书
Who's a clerk at the superior court
我告诉他关于提供情报的人的事
I told him about the informer
你要在8点和他见面
You must meet him at 8o'clock
如果他提供给我们能够缓刑的证据
If he gives any evidence to warrant a stay
我朋友说他会尽力帮助我们
My friend will hear us out
我们还是有希望阻止这一切
We still might be able to stop this
我得去告诉林肯
I gotta tell Lincoln
你要去那所监狱
You go to that prison
你知道 他们总会在你身边
They'll be all over you you know that.
他们总是想让我们疲于奔命
They've kept us on the run entired time.
因为我们把他公之与众 他们就完了
Because if anyone hears from us, we can do them damage
也许 我们在做着完全相反的事
Maybe it's time we do the exact opposite... go big
什么意思 大的?
What do you mean, "big"?
你的意思是找大媒体
You mean media big?
我们证据确凿
We got all the ammo we need
排起来有一公里长谋杀犯
There's a string of murders a mile long
受这件事的牵连 我们要揭露...
Connected to this.We will...
你已经准备好再一次面对媒体了吗? 呃?
Are you ready to show your face again? Huh?
你真的准备好了吗?
Are you ready for that?
事已至此 我们还能做什么其他的呢?
It's the bottom of the ninth.What else are we gonna do?
喂?
Hello?
喂 是爸爸 宝贝女儿
Hey. This is Daddy, baby girl.
爸爸
Daddy!
爸爸打来的电话
Daddy is on the phone.
骆驼怎么样啦?
How are the camels?
噢 好的 骆驼嘛 嗯 ...
Oh, well, the camels...
骆驼都很好
The camels are fine
我什么时候可以看见你?
When do I get to see you?
比我想象的要早
Earlier than I thought
爸爸说他很快就要回来了
Daddy said he's coming home soon
把电话拿给妈妈
Hey, put Mommy on the phone
谢谢你 甜心
Thank you, sweetie
第一军士 本杰明·迈尔斯·富兰克林
First Sergeant Benjamin Miles Franklin
你好吗?
How are you?
呃 宝贝...只是开卡车来打发时间
Oh, baby. Just driving trucks,eating dates
试着不让沙子钻进眼睛
Trying to keep the sand out of my eyes
那天我看了新闻
I saw on the news the other day
在科威特 华氏110度
It was 110 in Kuwait.
你肯定要被晒化了
You must be melting
在那
Over there
你不知道那里有多热
You have no idea
我听说你很快要回来了 是真的吗?
What's this about you coming home?
你是不会让女儿希望落空的 不是吗?
You're not getting your daughter's hopes up?
你坐稳了吗
You sitting down?
那是当然
Sure
你老公这周就能回到家
Your man is coming home this week
这周?
This week?
你说的是真的吗?
What are you talking about?
他们不是说你要
They said
明年才能回来
It'd be another year
嘿 命令已经下来了 宝贝
The orders just came down the pipe.
现在 我可不关心这里的温度是否降下来
And the hell if I care where they came down from.
我所关心的是
All that matters is
我们可以见面了
we will see each other
什么时候回来?什么时候?
When? When is this happening?
星期四 星期五 呃...我还不确定
Thursday, Friday. I'm not sure yet.
噢 我的上帝
Oh,my God!
要让我去机场接你回来吗?
Do you need me to pick you up from the airport?
噢 不 不 不要 呃...部队会负责到底的
Oh, no. No, no.The army's got that all that arranged
你知道的 你只要在家里等着我就好
You know, you just be waiting for me
好的 你知道我要让把它们全记下来
Well, you know I got that down
拜托 后退点?
Would you back up?
嘿 嘿 呃 你知道的 指挥官只让我多使用
Hey, you know, Comm is only letting me use this linkup
这电话机几分钟 所以 呃...
For a few more minutes
呃 戴里斯在吗?
Is Darius there?
我要和他说话
I need to speak to him
呃 在 在 我去叫他
Yeah, yeah. I'll go get him.
我爱你
I love you
我也爱你
I love you more
哟
Yo
哟 怎么啦 哥们?
Yeah, what's up, money?
你妹妹出去了吗?
Your sister out of the room?
是的
She is now
哥们 那外面到底是什么情形?
So, how is it out there, man?
狐狸河真的就像
Fox River all that
他们所说得那样?
They say it is?
不全是这样
Oh, man, it ain't all that
无论如何 不能太久
Not for long, anyway
你是什么意思?
What you mean by that?
我要你帮我做些事
I need you to do something for me
好 好 当然没问题
Yeah, all right.
你还是开那辆凯迪拉克攀登者吗?
You still drive that Escalader?
迈克尔·杰克逊还是白人吗?
Is Michael Jackson still white?
孩子 你就会开玩笑
Ha-ha, you gotjokes, son
能装多少人?
How many does it hold?
好的
OK
好什么?
OK what?
我们干吧
Let's do it
什么 你的意思是今晚?
What? You mean tonight?
那林肯怎么办?
What about Linc?
我需要一片剃刀刀片
I need a razor blade
迈克尔 一片剃刀刀片
A razor blade
也不能把他从里面弄出来
Ain't gonna get him out
你有还是没有?
Do you have one or not?
兄弟 小心
Careful, brother
引导我去接近水源
Leadeth me beside the still waters
修复我的灵魂
Restoreth my soul
请您引导我走上公正之路
Leadeth me in the path of righteousness for your sake
尽管我走在死亡阴影的山谷中...
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death
我不怕恶魔
I will fear no evil
我不怕恶魔 和我一同分享你的艺术
I will fear no evil.For thou art with me
你在我的敌人都在场的时候
In the presence of mine enemies
在我前面准备一张桌子
Thou preparest a table before me
当然 善良与仁慈...
Surely goodness and mercy
将一直伴随我们一生
Shall follow me all the days of my life
我们将永远受主的恩惠
And I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
阿门
Amen
他能听见我们的祈祷 你知道的 上帝
He does hear our prayers, the Lord...
是的
Yes
关于对林肯的支持
...on behalf of Lincoln
所有那些寻找宽恕的人们都将得到宽恕
All who seek forgiveness will be delivered
是的
Yes.
如果你兄弟接受了主的安排
If your brother accepts the Lord
他将得到永远的自由
He'll be free of this cage forever
是的
Yes
我将一直全程陪伴着他
I'll be available through this whole thing
如果你需要的话
If you need me
尊敬的牧师...
Reverend
尊敬的牧师 你能将这个给我哥哥吗?
Reverend, would you give this to my brother?
这对他意味着很多 他一看就知道是我给他的
It'd mean a lot to him,knowing it came from me
我会转交给他的
I will
那是我妈妈的
That was my mother's
告诉她 这将会使一个人摆脱痛苦
Tell her it's going to save someone a lot of pain
你确定你做这些有用吗?
You sure you know what you're doing?
这得看他的造化了
It's in God's hands now.
感觉好像你一直在给我作善后的事情
You've been the clean-up crew for me
我在这里的这段时间
The whole time I've been in here
脚趾受伤 打伤... 注射胰岛素
Toes, contusions, insulin shots
总得有人做吧
Well, somebody's gotta do it
非常感激
Well, I'm grateful
你还想过... 另一种生活...
You ever think, in another life...
我不会是那样的 女人 迈克尔
I won't be that woman, Michael
我不是要你成为那样
I wasn't asking you to be
但是 有些事
But it is something
我想知道
I wonder about
如果...
What if?
不管怎样 只是想确定你所说的
Anyway, just wanted to make sure it was said
为什么我的感觉就像是要跟你说再见?
Why do I feel like you're saying goodbye to me?
我不知道
I don't know
我想在象这样的地方
I guess in a place like this
你不会知道哪天才是你的最后一天
you never know which day is gonna be your last
莎拉 我这需要你的帮助
Sara, we got a backup out here.
好的
OK
你感觉下
You're set
我 呃...
I...
我对你哥哥的事表示遗憾
I'm sorry about your brother
医生...
Doctor...
谢谢
Thank you
兄弟 时间到了
This is it, brother
嘿
Hey
祝我们好运
Good luck to both of us
监狱工厂的 干活了!
PI! Let's do it!
你有没有弄明白啊?
Came to your senses, did you?
比如 你计算的神奇的方法
What did you figure a magic way
把你兄弟从那里弄出来
to get your brother out of that hole
和进入到警卫室里去
And into the guards' room?
他用不着去那里
He's not gonna be there
麻烦能把灯打开吗?
Could you put the light on?
你好吗?
You OK?
你在想什么 雷夫?
What do you think, Rev?
今天我和你弟弟谈了一次
I spoke with your brother today
他真诚为你做了祈祷
He's been praying for you
他一定非常的绝望
He must be desperate
你呢?
What about you?
你觉得绝望吗?
Are you feeling desperate?
不 只是让某些人绝望而已
No.Just for everyone else
那些你舍弃不顾的那些人
The ones you leave behind
那些我还没说再见的人
The ones I never got to say goodbye to
你知道的 我明天一直陪伴着你...
I can be with you all day tomorrow, you know.
包括那个时候
Right up to the time
谢谢
Thank you
嗯 他要我把这个给你
He wanted me to give this to you
迈克尔
Michael
她回来了
She's back in play
好的 谁和你在一起?
Good. Who's there with you?
唐格
Tangren
哈尔怎么样?
What about Hale?
迈阿密
Nope. MIA.
估计他也会在那里 你是什么意思 迈阿密?
He should be there. What do you mean, MIA?
我想这是一个相当简洁的说法
I think it's a fairly concise term
别接
Don't get it.
-飞机是几点的?  -11:00
-What time's the flight?  -11:00
别对任何人说 我要去 瑞格镇
Don't tell anyone.I gotta head up to Wrigleyville.
我两个小时候回来接你
I'll be back in a couple hours to collect you
现在确定东西都收拾好
Make sure you pack everything
一旦我们出了这扇门 我们就不再会回来
Once we're out that door,we won't come back
你要去干什么?
What are you gonna do?
有一封信要送
There's a letter I gotta deliver.
女士 你要退后点
听我说
Listen
我叫维罗妮卡·多诺万
I'm Veronica Donovan
我是林肯·布伦斯的代表律师
I represent Lincoln Burrows
很好 但现在不是谈这个的时候
Great, this isn't the time for it.
你必须靠边站
You'll have to step aside
呃 对不起 多诺万小姐?
I'm sorry.Miss Donovan?
你是不是说你是林肯·布伦斯的代表律师?
Did you say that you represent Lincoln Burrows?
林肯·布伦斯? 是的
Lincoln Burrows?That's right
安吉拉·维斯特 我是六频道新闻的主管
Angela West. I'm a producer with News Six
派得·派普(德国神话中吹笛带走老鼠的人) 下面怎么进行下去?
So, Mr Pied Piper, what's the play?
我们在做我们一直做的事: 假装工作
We do what we always do pretend to be working
假装良民 直到恰当的时候
Be model citizens...till the time comes
你说几点?
And that'd be?
9点
Nine o'clock
好像忘记了
You seem to be forgetting
工作时间好像是5点结束
That PI shuts down at five o'clock
那么我就得保证这没法按时结束 不是吗?
Well, we have to make sure it doesn't, don't we?
锤子
Hammer
哇 哇 你他妈的在干什么?
Whoa! What the hell are you doing, man?
这里到底发生了什么?
What the hell happened here?
混乱不堪 水管破了
Messed up. Hit a pipe
本应该在我们工作之前就该把水关掉 不是吗?
Should've killed the water Before we started?
应该吗?
Should've?
这可不是件麻烦的事
It's not that big a deal
我们可以在早晨之前修好它
We can fix it in the morning
我可不想
I don't think
石膏那时候就会发霉了
Mould should be a problem before then.
石膏?
Mould?
斯科菲尔德 闭嘴
Scofield.shut up, man
不 你闭嘴
You shut up
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
得把墙壁和木板都弄干
You get drywall and insulation soaked like this
否则石膏会发霉
You run the risk of stachybotrys mould
老大...
Boss
不太可能的 一千次中也最多就发生一次
that's just, like,one time in a thousand, for real
告诉你
Tell you what
你 还有你们几个
You and all your compa
你在这的同伴
Eros here
别想走出这个门一步
Aren't stepping outside this door
直到这该死的
Until every damn
每一滴水
Molecule of water
都不会从这再流出来
Is out of this place
那可得花上一晚上的功夫
It's gonna take all night
好啊 那你们就干一晚上
Well, then it's gonna take all night.
不要着凉啊
Don't catch a sniffle
你凶
Man
许多事情都要核查清楚
A lot of it checks out
她?
Put her on
多诺万小姐 如果你不介意
Miss Donovan.If you don't mind
我们想让你上镜受采访
We'd like to put you on
没问题 那就是我来这的原因
That's why I'm here
那就好 豪利 在这要
Great.Holly here
问你几个问题
Will be asking the questions
看他的手势 准备好了吗?
Just watch his hand, OK?
晚间新闻 皮特
Night NEWS Peter
在我身边的是维罗妮卡·多诺万 林肯·布伦斯的代理律师
I'm with Veronica Donovan,the lawyer for Lincoln Burrows
你正在为他作最后的努力 是吗?
You're petitioning for a stay, is that right?
是的
Yes
基于什么呢?
On what grounds?
我有充分的理由 我的当事人是被陷害的
On the grounds that my client was framed
把她的细节套出来
Get specifics
维罗妮卡·多诺万 你有什么充分而有力的证据吗?
Veronica Donovan.Do you have any proof?
有一条线索显示: 凶手...
There's a whole string of proof.Murders...
莱提卡·巴里斯 一个 知道真相的目击证人
Leticia Barris.A potential exculpatory witness
莉萨·利克斯
Lisa Rix
林肯的妻子
The mother of Lincoln's child
比斯霍普·迈克莫罗 他
Bishop McMorrow
已经向联邦政府提出重审请求
Who could have petitioned for clemency
你是说有别人杀了他们 而嫁祸别人?
Someone's killing these people off?
我的意思是有人想掩盖事实的真相
I'm saying somebody's trying to hide what happened
特伦斯·斯蒂德曼的事实 真相到底是怎样
The truth about Terrence Steadman
这些只是你得推测 还是有了强而有力
Is this all just speculation, or is there hard evidence
支持你推断的证据?
To substantiate your claims?
我有根据
I have a source
要他的名字
Get a name
你现在的心情是不是非常的复杂?
Could you elaborate?
不是现在这个时候 但是有人现在在监狱里
No.Somebody on the inside
坚持声称他是无辜的 应当被无罪释放
Claims they can exonerate Lincoln,that Terrence Steadman wasn't in the car that night
有人已经说出来了
Someone's been talking
是用直流电吗?
Is there a reason you're on direct current?
怎么了?
Sorry?
你知道 交流电/直流电
You know, AC/DC.
换电流 用直流电
Alternating current, direct current.DC's kinda
直流电比较落后
Yesterday's news for this sort of thing
你可以只用交流电的一半能量就可以处死那个人
You can kill a man with half the energy if you go AC
好的
OK
看看我们干的
Let's see what we got
准备好了吗?
You ready to run one?
警官们 我认为最好把这些灯打开
Sir.I think you better turn these lights on.
小姐 我们不能这么做
Miss.Can't do it
你的当事人正在被关禁闭
Your client's being disciplined
你触犯了我当事人的合法权利
You're violating his Eighth Amendment rights
你要么5秒钟后把灯打开
Either you turn those lights on at next five seconds.
要么你就准备作被告
Or you'll be the first defendant named in a lawsuit
你好吗?
You OK?
我儿子好吗?
LJ?
他很好
He's good
他很担心你 但是现在他很好
He's scared, but he's good
我找到一个可以救你的证人
I found someone who's gonna talk
-谁?  -我不认识 但是他知道一些内幕
-Who?  -I don't know.But he knows something
我几个小时后就去与他见面
But I'll meet him in a few hours
宝贝 几个小时候我就要被执行死刑了
A few hours is cutting it close
我们没有其他的选择
We don't have any other choice
你必须要有坚定的信念 好吗?
You have to have faith, OK?
尼克已经准备接受我们的案子
Nick's already primed the court to hear our case
无论迈克尔要做什么?他现在不需要再这么做了
Whatever Michael's doing,he doesn't need to do it now
我们会用最好的方法去就解决这件事
We'll beat this the right way
如果你错了 怎么办?
What if you're wrong?
我不会错的
I'm not
如果?
What if you are?
你必须要相信我 好吗?
You gotta trust me, OK?
千万不要放弃
Don't give up on me
保证
Promise?
没有吓到你吧
Didn't mean to scare you
没有 没事
No. It's all right
-保罗 你好吗?  -我很好
-Paul, how are you?  -I'm good
我很好
I'm good
你呢?
You?
你这要去哪?
Where you going?
旅行 巴哈马
Vacation.Bahamas
带这么多东西去巴哈马?
Packing kinda heavily for the Bahamas.
你知道的 女人嘛
You know women
是
Yeah
所以 呃...
So...
丹尼去哪了?
where's Danny?
呃 我想是跑出去办事了
Running errands, I think.
办事 呃?
Errands, huh?
哪里啊...去哪里办事阿?
Where... where might those errands be?
路易斯 是你吗?
Lewis, you there?
是啊 是啊 我在这
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here, Linc.
你几点下班?
What time you got?
8点多一点
A little after eight.
已经8: 15
It's 8:15
你没事吧?
You OK?
不
No.
噢 迈克尔
Oh, Michael
9点 嫩鸡
Nine o'clock, fish.
该出发了
Showtime
伙计 我们出发
Let's go, man
唐克雷蒂 已经下班了吗?
Tancredi leave yet?
不 我想她还没走
I don't think so.
你最好去叫她
You better call her.
外面见了
See you on the other side.
好像是食物中毒
Well, everything tells me it's food poisoning,
你在未来两个小时内
In a couple of hours
会感觉好点 但是 呃...
Which means you should feel better
我希望我说的会让你在
But...I wish I could say
行刑前感到好过点
That this would be enough to forestall the execution
其实不会那样
It's not gonna be
好的 我知道
It's all right
如果你需要我 我可以一直陪着你
I can stay with you if you want.
不
No
我很好 谢谢
It's fine. Thank you
好的
OK
我们关于这件事有很多东西要谈 但是却没那么多时间
We got a lot to talk about and not a lot of time to do it.
你男朋友... 他还能救
Your boyfriend, he can still be saved.
布伦斯 他之前就被选中
Burrows was chosen a long time ago
他是被钦点的替死鬼
Hand-picked to be an assassin
但是他从来就没开过枪
But he never pulled the trigger
到底是谁做的
Who did?
快告诉我
Come on
到底是谁杀了特伦斯·斯蒂德曼?
Who killed Terrence Steadman?
没有人
Nobody
什么?!
What?
特伦斯·斯蒂德曼现在还活着
Terrence Steadman's still alive.
在这里面有三张纸
There's three sheets of paper inside.
你可以找到
You'll find all the names
你所需要的所有人的名单
You need are on them
包括开始这件事的每一个人
Everyone that started this whole thing
从上到下
From top to bottom
马上躲到车后面去
You need to take two steps that way,right now
躲到车后面去
Behind the car. Get behind the car
你还想活下去吗? 照我说的做
You want to stay alive, do as I say
马上
Now
你们在这真不错 快点走
Your boys better be there, rug　head.
他们很快就回来了 克鲁图斯 不要你担心
They'll be there, cleatis. Don't you worry
哥们 这太疯狂了
This is crazy
所以 呃...丹尼 你在这干什么呢?
So, what are you doing here, Danny?
那个律师在哪?
Where's the lawyer?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about
艾利森 已经都告诉我了
Allison told me
我从她那都知道了
I got it out of her
你别动她
You didn't touch her?
我为什么要那样做呢?
Why would I do that?
我们是搭档 不是吗?
We're partners, right?
我们是一条船上的
We're on the same side
不
No
艾利森 她没事
Allison's fine
她只是...
She's just...
好的 我猜想你要
OK.I guess you wanna...
好好的问自己谁才是 你要放弃的...
You're gonna have to ask yourself who you want to give up
你妻子还是那个律师
Your wife, or this lawyer
只要告诉我她在哪里
Just tell me where she is
她在这么?
Is she here?
还是刚刚在?
Has she been?
你到底要...
What exactly have you told...
千万别这么做
Don't do this
把你的枪给我
Give me your gun
-不能那么做  -是的 你可以的
-I can't do that  -Yes, you can
我是你的上司
I'm your superior
这是命令 你必须服从
I give you a command. You obey it.
把枪给我
Give me your gun
保罗 这什么也不是 这没什么的...
Paul, it's nothing. It's not...
别动
Don't. Back up
太令人惊奇了
It's amazing
你已经都把它弄在...这三张纸上了
You got it all on only... three pages
你知道的如果这些纸落入其他人的手中
If this fell into the wrong hands?
会发生什么吗?
You know what would happen
你把我也写上去了?
You named me?
和其他人列在一起?
Right there along with the rest of them?
伙计 我好怕
I got scared
那已经是这样了 你敢把我也列上去
That's all it was. You named me?
-丹尼?  -求求你 伙计!
-Danny. -Please, man!
艾利森还一个月就生了
Allison's due in one month.
保罗 你和我 我们 从中学就是朋友
Paul, you and me,we-we've been friends since the academy.
可你把我也写上去了
You named me
好了 快上来
OK. Let's go
嗨 嗨 嗨
Hey, hey, hey
伙计 把那个收起来
Put that away, man
你在干嘛? 伙计 把那个收起来
What you doing? Put that away, man
嘿 你们两个
Hey, yo-yos
这里是监狱的禁区
This is a state penitentiary
你们不能把车停在这
You can't park here
噢 你认为我们想把车停在这吗?
You think we meant to park here?
把手放到我可以看见的地方
Put your hands where I can see them
我再说一遍 把手放到我能看见的地方
I said put your hands where I can see them
修好了
All fixed
你们立刻离开这里
What do you say you two hit the road?
你们立刻离开这里 立刻...
You two hit the road right now
或者我们将让你们有麻烦
Or we're gonna have a problem
还好吗?
You all right?
我很好
I'm good
从来没有像现在这么好
Haven't been this good in years
迈克尔...
Michael?
他在那里
He's there
狗娘养的...
Son of a bitch!
他在那里
He's there
这 迈克尔 用这个
Here, Michael. Use this
你准备好了吗?
Come on! You ready?
准备好了吗?
Ready?
怎么了 和我说
What? Talk to me
我办不到
It can't be done
什么?
What?
它太厚了
It's too thick
对不起
I'm so sorry
我们从这里出不去
We're not getting out of here
不幸的 哥们 我们别无选择
Unfortunately, pretty,that ain't an option